https://felinesnoozers.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.It is Feline Snoozer’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.THIRD PARTY ANALYTICS PROVIDERS, AD SERVERS AND SIMILAR THIRD PARTIES We may work with advertising agencies and vendors who use technology to help us understand how people use our Site. These vendors may use technologies to serve you advertisements that may interest you. You can choose to opt out of receiving interest-based advertising by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Feline Snoozers may change this privacy policy from time to time at Feline Snoozer’s sole discretion.
